We're going to have the education, but I'll back to the first person to interpret it.
Ready?
Thank you.
Didn't want to do that.
Let's pray together.
I think you're so grateful for all of you.
You should give us a family of friends.
This is a gift of community that we share here.
We have to give us hearts of service that we would remember always with whatever decision we make that we go out to one another.
And we go out to you.
Let's be service.
We ask you Jesus name.
Amen.
I'd like to please you to do the life of the United States and to do the Republic of the United States.
One nation.
I don't know about any of this.
We'll let it redeem in us tomorrow.
Before we'll tell the kids about this, give us personal care to you.
We have to do it for the one on that.
Five.
Is that the agenda?
Stand for it in the end.
We have a group of five.
Six.
And seven.
Two.
One.
Five.
Six.
Nine.
Five.
Six.
Seven.
Five.
Nine.
Six.
Four.
Five.
Right.
And she sent her survey out to the host of the cities
in Oklahoma that they'd go with.
Three top choices come back to us to investigate.
One was paymentless.
One was in voice E-cloud.
One was paying seconds.
Paymentless had a clear advantage over the other two
because they could integrate our software system.
And so we began to wrap.
We got close to paying seconds.
We got close to E-cloud.
Paymentless would not only integrate,
but they also beat the other two in their close.
Currently, we will live official finance center at the last month of the OPC, they charge $5.95
per $400 in transactions.
What pay-in-sickets has proposed is $4.95 for first $600 in transactions.
So up to $600, or up to $400, we'll get a $1 reduction for the customers from $4600
to $6.95 savings, and the savings grow only to get higher bills.
Currently, the OPC is there.
There is only one fee for each extra, and that's $5.95 for $1.95 each extra.
Pay-in-sickets could not match that, but they get $4.95 for $3,000 in transaction on each extra.
Pay-in-scuses offers multiple ways to pay.
They offer Walmart pay, then they'll pay to have credit, pay to have Amazon pay, and Amazon
Lyself pay.
I can say, they will be straight up.
In total, there's a cost of that.
It's $3,645.
Pay-in-scuses has a great pay that installation of first-year, and it will be a $1.95 fee for the Lyself
but it will be less than $1,000 a year for the Lyself going forward.
We do recommend that the Lyself is contract with Pay-in-Scuses that will take up to 90 days
to change that up.
We would probably shoot before and it will allow you to change over, completely.
Start with the Lyself.
Pay-in-scuses.
We would run a side by side, initially, to get people to switch to over.
We can't create it.
We can't store your data.
We don't put it in your data every time.
Hopefully, we can do that over the next three months.
And by July 1, we can make a visual switch to where.
Pay-in-scuses will be the only way to get it.
Other than coming inside and doing the banking of the Lyself,
I can find it through the phone.
That'll be the only way to get it.
I'll be glad to answer your question that you had.
It's mentioned there.
The key-offs.
Is that something that we can set up here?
Well, there was a lot of talk about putting the key-offs in one point.
If we do put in a key-offs at some point,
Pay-in-scuses can't be the process for that key-offs.
With the mobility of Pay-in-scuses.
the C.A.S. I don't believe it.
Is there an act?
It goes with that as well.
At this point, I'm not aware of act.
It's at the west side of those, and it is,
it is a magnitude mobile, so it will show up properly on your phone.
What's the link to the contract that we signed in the previous year?
There, I'm not aware of it.
It's a leap of time of the contract.
Since it's not the city that's paying it,
it doesn't matter where you're going to be sitting,
all of the years.
So it's a totally national.
It's going to be more than the moon.
Did you see your balance on your side?
From the preliminary course, you can't see your balance through the record.
You will not be 100%.
Conely.
So if you come in and make a payment to in-house,
you're going to be at the same as you walk up the door.
It will not update until we send the next million update.
Thank you.
It's a lot of different options.
Making payment with the bank balance,
and then the one where I'm going to be used,
but make out with them.
I mean, both of those are fairly easy.
So, I think you've got those.
It's people other options.
Yes, sir.
There's an on the $600 transaction.
Our average transaction is $300.
So if we're on about $600 transaction,
that handle $96% of our customers.
If you get a volume,
somewhere between $1,150 and $150 and $5,
this will actually be cheaper than paying in-house with a credit card.
So what if the person's utility bills will do them at $10,000,
and $10,000 on the 10,000?
$10,000?
$15,000.
They still consider them in common to not,
or consider the insurance.
We accept that.
So it's shut off for us today.
We're not talking to more and more and more before anybody is shut off.
So we would get those.
Since it's integrated in-house,
it's going to come in automatically.
There's not a chance.
in addition time.
Well, I've got all the back to say it and push it on through, but it'll come in every
night at certain times.
It's midnight or whatever.
All the signs I should put that day to come in, all I need to know, I said somebody
is having to approve it and post it.
So my question was, will there be a supposed to take that with the deadline?
It's my 12th in March 10th, and I've paid it 1159 on March 10th.
You might have to worry about giving that to people that even on the chart.
As long as it's transferred to us tonight, we'll know that shut off of concrete.
It may not or two in the morning or whatever.
All this transport does.
Eight o'clock in the morning, there is no face for you.
Thank you.
All right.
Maran, et cetera.
Check.
All of the associations.
Work order.
19.
16.
20.
8.
And then number one.
First data.
Structure.
And then.
So this is.
Part two.
So we was here.
And I want to go.
Get the award for black.
Point work.
This is the observation piece of it.
Or also.
Keep an eye on it.
Make sure to follow this back.
We're supposed to do.
And if you guys get much pain.
It's an hourly comment right.
You're just like the one with that now.
We don't spend it.
You don't see a real.
And I've been saying that.
Like, right.
There's a second turn.
And we know that.
And we know that all day.
I'll try to go to the sites.
Talk about some different things.
We go a lot.
I'm going in a very younger company.
It's a rich man.
You know.
I mean.
But they work for.
They have.
Also they're a lot.
They don't have.
The large.
They can get low.
They can.
And they.
They work out.
They're on.
And for this.
46,000 years.
Going to put it.
A side.
And use it.
Yeah.
So basically.
So the meeting.
I have.
When our students.
They're staying down.
Basically.
That money comes out of that.
But.
And then.
We're supposed to do.
It's weekly or highly clean coordination policy and project, so that project will help cover
the time for the engineers to coordinate with the contractor to get to that.
I think they come in towards the end of the project and then once in the middle and kind of look everything over and make sure that we're all on the same page.
So this quarter six thousand earmarked to the end of the fiscal year.
Actually, I think the schedule was like September and it really depends on the end of the project.
So we'll basically end up re-encumbering some of this to cover the industry.
But yeah, this should be the end of the construction project.
Plus whatever we've had in the span of the time.
So we're going to use that one too.
But I don't want to see this using all of it.
If you want a little further motion, there's a little bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit.
So if you've done several things, work it, work it.
I think I heard the title.
Hi guys.
Thank you.
The Dan Brewer, we're going to go reject sector four capital layout for requests for Tyler.
Yes, I thought this is something that's usually done.
I don't even have any questions behind, but I'm here again using the manager.
You guys know we brought the first order out to your approval.
Now we're going to take a second.
This year, hopefully it'll all be a pretty long time.
And it might have to tell us like, eight and a five and a seven.
First order of the time.
The thought was back to the end is that, you know, it was the new city manager coming in.
You know, I think it's probably what we thought it did.
But to let them come in and see what all we're doing.
I can talk about it in the comments on that.
Some of them are, you know, we have some big projects as far as six payment water line,
a part of water town, a little bit of building.
Down to down street, you know, which hopefully some of those on the 69.
There's a lot of some degrees of water.
Question out there in the area.
We have.
So the lighting on the Q&A, short list.
We have a lot of eye eye.
So we have a lot of back there.
And the super there.
There's a people that we talk to since I've been here.
If they were nice enough, you know, when I heard great,
I'd like to have a headache like this.
We can even get closer to those because of this.
I'm fine.
So this will hopefully be great from then.
You know, it's a whole line of probably a year old line.
There's a team that we have 300,000 before.
We place them in a infrastructure like we can go down in the South West to go down.
I don't know how I'm 25.
You see how many holes are there in there?
I'm pretty good.
And those holes have been there for a long time.
We're making a significant investment in it.
I got an interest in this number.
So I find it to the radio that we have.
It's going to be a good group.
I'll say.
Hard group.
Good.
Thank you.
For 11 other new business to many of those reasons as opposed to this agenda.
12 staff reports.
13 trust.
It may be an ambulance.
Or a trustee can be an ambulance.
14 in Germany.
Second.
4.
8.
9.